rechargeableplanet.com 2009-06-15

# Rechargeable Planet - Privacy Policy

Rechargeable Planet RESPECTS YOUR PRIVACY

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to you, our customer. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for this site, RechargeablePlanet.com.

  * We do not rent our mailing list to 3rd parties.
  * We only send email and postal mail to those who have elected to receive it from us. You can opt-out of receiving these notices at any time.
  * We will not give any information about you to others without your express permission.

Our site uses forms in which you give us contact information (your name, address, daytime telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, and request information and support. 

If you choose to order from us using a credit card, we will collect your credit card number and expiration date. 

If you contact us for support, we will keep an internal record of what support was given. 

We use your customer information only when it will be important for us to contact you regarding changes to our products, our web site, new Rechargeable Planet services, and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, you may opt-out at any time.

If we present a co-branded offer with our partners or affiliates, it will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the information and whose privacy statement applies.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

We use information gathered about you from our site statistics (for example your IP address) to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.

**SENDING EMAILS**  
We use emails to communicate with you, to confirm your placed orders, and to send information that you have requested. We also provide email links, as on our E-Mail Link, to allow you to contact us directly. We strive to promptly reply to your messages. The information you send to us may be stored and used to improve this site and our products, or it may be reviewed and discarded. 

**ONLY IF WE HAVE TO**  
As stated previously in this policy, we will not share your personal information except with a third party to assist us in the processing or securing of your personal information or when we are required by law unless we have given you notice and choice, in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our web site. 

**CHANGES IN OUR PRACTICES**  
If we make material changes to our information handling practices or other privacy aspects, we will post those changes on this privacy statement, or  
notify you directly via email. Minor changes will be immediately effective upon reposting to this privacy policy on the website.
